

519 500 8887 t.hackbart@gmail.com Waterloo Ontario
GitHub: tylerhackbart LinkedIn: LinkedIn.com/in/TylerHackbart Portfolio: tylerhackbart.com

Applicant Overview

I am a motivated, responsible front-end developer with a diverse work background who cares deeply about design and user experience. I am excited by companies that are building meaningful products and disruptive technologies. I have a dedicated, farm-raised work ethic coupled with a passion for crafting amazing user interactions.

Skills

- Proficient in Ruby, Rails framework, jQuery, JavaScript, HTML5/ CSS, Node, Git & GitHub and Object Oriented Design, through educational experience at Bitmaker Labs
- Experience in Swift for iOS platform, Adobe Creative Suite and Responsive Design
- Practical knowledge of how a start up runs, working on different teams of start up companies
- Excellent interpersonal and communication skills resulting for experience in various human service roles

Relevant Experience

IOS DEVELOPER – APR 2014 - CURRENT JUICEBOX MONKEY, WATERLOO ONTARIO

- Application design firm that I co-foundered earlier this year, that specialize in iOS applications written in Objective C and Swift
- Applications that we are creating range from informational, server based and application games for the iPad, iPhone and Apple Watch

WEB APPLICATION DEVELOPER - OCT 2014 - CURRENT

DATE IN A BOX, WATERLOO ONTARIO

- Job entails design and programming both mobile and desktop sites, written with Ruby
- Very early stage of start up, currently working on first version of both the web application and mobile app for the iOS platform

IOS DEVELOPER - AUG 2014 -DEC 2014

GRANDEZVOUS, TORONTO ONTARIO

- Designing and programming the GrandezVous application for the iOS platform
- Languages used are Objective C, as well as testing with Swift

FRONT END DEVELOPER INTERN - APR 2014 - AUG 2014

BLURBI, TORONTO ONTARIO

- Converted photoshop mockups of numerous webpages throughout <u>blurbi.ca</u>
- Languages used were HTML,CSS, Bootstrap frameworks, and Node.js

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE - JUN 2013 - CURRENT

STAPLES CANADA, WATERLOO ONTARIO

- Expanded to all available positions early on, originally hired as technology sales
- Occasional technical work; setting up the personal interface for customer computers, running virus scans and data wipes of units

Education

Bitmaker Labs, Toronto Ontario – 9 Week Immersive Web Developer - 2014

Elmira Secondary High School, Elmira Ontario – Diploma – 2007 - 2012